Guide to the Architectural Drawings and Maps of Yale University Buildings and Grounds
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Architectural drawings and maps (not microfilmed), Series II
  - 11:17 Dept. of University Health, Plans (2). Copies, 1929 October (Folder 632)
  - 11:19 Stoeckel Hall (96 Wall St.), Heating Diagram, 1955 April 14 (Folder 633)
  - 11:23 302 Temple St. (4 drawings), undated (Folder 428)
  - 11:23 Yale University Press (302 Temple St)
    - 3 drawings, 1961, 1964 (Box 679)
    - 7 drawings, 1988 (Folder 833)
  - 11:24 Corbey Court
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (9 drawings), 1967-1979 (Box 754)
  - 11: Elm Street, elevation between College and Church Streets, undated (Folder 589)
  - 11: Blueprint of Elm-College-Wall-Temple block, 1928 (Box 713)
  - 11: (Slifka, Joseph) Jewish Community Center (80 Wall St)
    - Preliminary design, Design development I and II, 50% Construction Documents, 90% construction documents I and II, Construction Document Addendum (Deborah Berke), 1998 February - 1999 January (Box 743)
    - Preliminary design, Design development I and II, 50% Construction Documents, 90% construction documents I and II, Construction Document Addendum (Deborah Berke), 1998 February - 1999 January (Box 744)
  - 12:8 Sheffield Scientific Hall #1, partial elevations, circa 1902 (Folder 827)
  - 12:22 St. Anthony's Hall, Stair Plan. Copy, Undated (Folder 630)
  - 12:22 250 Church St. (4 drawings), undated (Folder 429)
  - 12:24 258 Church St. (5 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 12:26 Timothy Dwight College (345 Temple St)
    - mostly kitchen plans (12 drawings), undated (Box 431)
    - 49 drawings, undated (Box 432)
    - Assignment Plans, 1999; 19
    - Maps, 1999; 4
    - Space Data, 1999; computer file (XLS)
    - Comprehensive Renovation (Box 741)
    - Plans and Elevation data, 1999 (Box 741)
    - Proposal - Gisoffi, 2000 January 31 (Box 741)
    - Preliminary - schematic design, 2000 May (Box 741)
  - 12:28 Silliman College (505 College St)
    - Architectural Details, Miscellaneous, 1939-1940 (Box 802)
    - Architectural Details, 1939-1940 (Box 804)
    - Architectural Sketches, 1939-1940 (Box 807)
    - Architectural Sketches, 1939-1940 (Box 809)
    - Architectural Sketches, 1939-1940 (Box 789)
    - Gate Details, 1940 (Box 810)
    - Gates and Fence (Shop Drawings), 1940 (Folder 812)
    - Mantels (Shop Drawings), 1940 (Box 811)
    - Plans (12). Copies, 1931 (Folder 630)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 840)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 841)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 842)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 843)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 844)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 845)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 846)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 847)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 848)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 849)
    - Architectural Details: Drawing #s 301-425, 1001-1103, 1939-1940 (Box 850)
  - 12:29 St. Anthony Hall (2 drawings), undated (Folder 434)
  - 13:5 Winchester Hall: ironwork detail (1 drawing), undated (Folder 435)
  - 13:6 51 Prospect St., undated
    - Original floor plans, Cady, Berg, and See, 1894 (Folder 436)
    - Arthur K. Watson Hall, complete renovation & restoration drawing set, 1984 (Folder 437)
    - Plan of footings; Cady, Berg and See, circa 1894 (Box 574)
  - 13:8 Leet Oliver Memorial Hall (12 Hillhouse Ave) (8 drawings), undated (Folder 438)
  - 13:9 Dunham Laboratory (10 Hillhouse Ave)
    - 12 drawings, undated (Box 431)
    - 3 drawings, 1964 (Box 679)
  - 13:16 Sheffield-Sterling-Strathcona Hall [Sheffield Scientific School] (1 Prospect St)
    - 4 drawings, undated (Box 431)
    - Survey of Sheffield Square of the Sheffield Scientific School, 1915 January (Folder 638)
    - Map of Electrical Engineering Laboratory Site for Sheffield Scientific School, 1912 June 25 (Folder 638)
    - Drawing of the Easterly Portion of the Sheffield Scientific School, 1907 August 23 (Folder 638)
    - Tracing of the Easterly Portion of the Sheffield Scientific School, from the above drawing, 1955 February 25 (Folder 638)
    - Property map of the Sheffield Scientific School, 1928 November (Folder 638)
    - 1st Floor Plan (1) and 1st Floor Plan Copy (1), undated (Folder 630)
    - Sheffield Laboratory: linen tracings and prints showing previous renovations; Cady, Berg and See (Folder 831)
  - 13:18 Engineering and Science Building (Box 770)
  - 13: 10, 12 Prospect Street
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (20 drawings), 1979-1988 (Box 755)
  - 14: Whitney Grove housing presentation drawings (22), 1972 (Folder 608)
  - 14:4 Mason Laboratory (10 drawings), undated (Folder 441)
  - 14:7 432-434 Temple (2 drawings), 1972 (Box 679)
  - 14:7 442 Temple St. (1 drawing), undated (Box 431)
  - 14:15 370 Temple St. (3 drawings), undated (Box 431)
  - 14:25 Yale Health Center
    - Project Approval Architectural Drawings, 1930 (Box 811)
  - 14:31 88 Trumbull; L.H. Jones (4 tracings), 1932 (Folder 585)
  - 15: 12 Mansfield Street
    - Floor plans, transparency, 1948 September 16 (Folder 634)
    - Assignment plans, 1982 (Folder 682)
  - 15:2 Hammond Hall (14 Mansfield St): valve and fixtures (4 drawings), undated (Folder 447)
  - 15:9 Social Science Library (140 Prospect St.)
    - Renderings (2 drawings), undated (Folder 448)
    - Assignment Plan - First Floor and Ramp Addition (2 drawings), Undated (Box 852)
    - Basement, First Floor Stat Lab and Second Floor (3 drawings), Undated, 1993 (Box 853)
    - Renovation Working Plans (2 drawings), 1977 (Box 854)
    - Working Plans (7 drawings), 1977 (Box 855)
      General Note
      Drawings include note: "Includes drawings of drain for ramp (revised 7/29/91)"
  - 15:9 Berkeley Divinity School (140 Prospect St.)
    - 15:9 Berkeley Divinity School, Floor Plans (2), Elevations and Cross Sections (1), undated (Folder 632)
    - 15:9 Berkeley Divinity School, Blueprints for Heating and Plumbing (1), 1956 (Box 856)
  - 15:17 Seeley G. Mudd Library (38 Mansfield St)
    - Floor plans for basement, ground floor, first floor, second floor, third floor, and penthouse and roof plan (5 drawings), 1985 August (Box 626)
    - Mounted presentation drawings, undated (Folder 449)
    - Mounted presentation drawings, undated (Folder 450)
    - Mounted presentation drawings, undated (Folder 451)
    - Mounted presentation drawings, undated (Folder 452)
    - Mounted presentation drawings, undated (Folder 453)
    - Mounted presentation drawings, undated (Folder 454)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 456)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 458)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 459)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 461)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 463)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 465)
    - Blueprints, undated (Box 466)
    - Tracing paper originals and miscellaneous, undated (Folder 468)
    - Tracing paper originals and miscellaneous, undated (Folder 469)
    - Tracing paper originals and miscellaneous, undated (Folder 470)
    - Tracing paper originals and miscellaneous, undated (Folder 471)
    - Tracing paper originals and miscellaneous, undated (Folder 472)
    - Presentation drawings (3), undated (Box 578A–578B, Folder 578)
    - First Floor Plans (2 drawings), Undated (Box 857)
    - Early Plans (5 drawings), Undated (Box 858)
    - Stacks Plans (3 drawings), Undated (Box 859)
    - Stacks Plans (2 drawings), Undated (Box 860)
    - Furnishing Details (2 drawings), Undated (Box 861)
    - Furnishing Details (1 drawing), Undated (Box 862)
  - 15: 162 Prospect St., Floor Plans (4), 1942 August 12 (Folder 630)
  - 16:1 School of Organization and Management (135 Prospect St): mounted presentation drawings (2 drawings), undated (Folder 473)
  - 16:2 28 Hillhouse Avenue: office alterations (1 drawing), undated (Box 474)
  - 16:5 77 Prospect St.: alterations (6 drawings), undated (Folder 475)
  - 16:7 87 Trumbull St.
    - alterations (5 drawings), undated (Box 474)
    - R.W. Foote (18 tracings), 1930-1932 (Folder 588)
  - 16:9 20 Hillhouse Avenue: floor plans (4 drawings), undated (Box 423)
  - 16:10 135 Prospect St.: fire escape drawing (1 drawing), undated (Folder 478)
  - 16:12 46 Hillhouse Avenue: landscape plan (1 drawing), undated (Folder 479)
  - 16: Yale Astronomy Center (60 Sachem St.), Proposed Alteration Plan, 1965 December 13 (Folder 633)
  - 16: 85, 88 Trumbull Street
    - Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (27 drawings), 1932-1981 (Box 756)
  - 16: 87 Trumbull St (2 drawings), 1968 (Folder 833)
  - 17:1 31 Hillhouse Avenue (President Noah Porter): floor plans (4 drawings), undated (Box 480)
  - 17:5 John North House (158 Whitney Ave)
    - plans (14 drawings), undated (Box 480)
    - L.H. Jones (5 tracings), 1937 (Folder 651)
  - 17:6 51 Hillhouse; R.W. Foote (2 tracings), 1927 (Folder 584)
  - 17:7 55 Whitney Avenue: plans (3 drawings), undated (Folder 482)
  - 17: Block bounded by Whitney, Hillhouse, and Sachem. Sketch, undated (Folder 631)
  - 18:5 Yale Computer Center (175 Whitney Ave) (1 drawing), undated (Box 480)
  - 19:3 314 Prospect St.: plans (5 drawings), undated (Box 480)
  - 19:5 168 Prospect St.
    - Basement floor plan, 1942 August 11 (Folder 634)
    - First Floor Plan, undated (Folder 634)
    - Second Floor plan, 1942 August 14 (Folder 634)
    - Third Floor plan, 1942 August 14 (Folder 634)
    - Basement, undated (Folder 634)
    - 3rd Floor, 1934 November 20 (Folder 634)
    - 1st Floor, undated (Folder 634)
    - 2nd Floor, undated (Folder 634)
  - 19:8 202 Prospect (4 tracings), circa 1931 (Folder 583)
  - 19:11 204 Prospect St.
    - plans (8 drawings), undated (Box 480)
    - L.H. Jones (5 tracings), 1932 (Folder 582)
  - 19:19 William B. Greeley Memorial Laboratory (370 Prospect St): (2 drawings), undated (Box 480)
  - 19:20 254 Prospect; L.W. Robinson (19 tracings), 1911 (Folder 586)
  - 19:24 386 Prospect St. (Esplanade Apartments): plans (8 drawings), undated (Box 480)
  - 19:25 218 Prospect Street: floor plans (4 drawings), undated (Box 480)
  - 19: 202 Prospect St, undated (Folder 835)
  - 20:1 Sloan Physics Laboratory: electrical (1 drawing), undated (Box 490)
  - 20:2 Osborn Memorial Lab
    - Basement Plan #9617; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Foundation Plan #9631; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - First Floor Plan #9621; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Basement Plan #9617 [second copy]; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Floor Plan - ? [torn sheet]; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Foundation Plan #9638; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - First Floor Plan #9621 [second copy]; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Plan of rooms 150 and 200A #9904; Charles C. Haight, 1913 February (Folder 649)
    - Sub-basement Plan #9631; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Section through driveway; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Statement of required register openings [5 plans, 12 sheets]; Charles C. Haight, 1912 June (Folder 649)
    - Block Plan showing grade levels of buildings; Charles C. Haight, 1911 December (Folder 649)
    - (Sloane Physics Laboratory - Section A-B) [torn sheet]; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Zoology Wing #9629; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - Block Plan and borings - Albert B. -Hill, Consulting Engineer; Charles C. Haight, 1912 January (Folder 649)
    - Basement, first floor, second floor plans [one sheet]; Charles C. Haight, 1912 March (Folder 649)
    - Third floor and attic plans [one sheet]; Charles C. Haight, 1912 March (Folder 649)
    - North elevation in Quadrangle; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - West elevation [torn sheet]; Charles C. Haight (Folder 649)
    - 41 drawings, undated (Box 474)
    - 41 drawings, undated (Box 490)
  - 20:3 Pierson Sage Boiler and Refrigeration Plant
    - Proposed greenhouse, 1963 (Folder 834)
    - Power Plant (2 drawings), 1962 (Folder 832)
  - 20:5 Sterling Chemistry Laboratory (225 Prospect St)
    - 8 drawings, undated (Folder 493)
    - Southwest - Demolition, new work, elevations and sections, reflected ceiling plan, and finish and miscellaneous schedules (5 drawings), 1987 February 20
    - 3 drawings, undated (Box 679)
    - 1947 1947 (Folder 834)
    - Detail of black slate tablet on vellum, 1938 October 27 (Box 911)
  - 20:6 Peabody Museum of Natural History (170 Whitney Ave)
    - 13 drawings, undated (Box 474)
    - Bingham Laboratory: Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (91 drawings), 1952-1988 (Box 753)
    - Bingham Laboratory: Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (91 drawings), 1952-1988 (Box 757)
    - Bingham Laboratory: Original construction documents, alterations, and assignment plans (91 drawings), 1952-1988 (Box 758)
    - Architectural Prints, 1923 (Box 813)
    - Contractor Prints, 1923-1924 (Box 787)
    - Architectural Details, 1923-1924 (Box 818)
    - Architectural Details, 1923-1924 (Box 819)
    - Proposed addition, drawing by George Spansler, 1930-05-08; Reproduction [?] mounted on mason board; 54 inches X 21 inches. (Folder 913)
  - 20:7 Sage Hall (including Bowers Hall)
    - 7 drawings, undated (Folder 495)
    - Set of pencil drawings (4) on tissue, of the "Proposed Yale Forestry School," by the architectural firm, Cram, Goodhue and Ferguson, circa 1900 (Folder 652)
  - 20:9 340 Edwards St. (4 drawings), undated (Box 465)
  - 20:13 Linear Electron Accelerator (?), Bench Plan, 1953 November 24 (Folder 630)
  - 20:14 Josiah Willard Gibbs Laboratory (9 drawings), undated (Box 465)
  - 20:16 334 Edwards St. (4 drawings), undated (Box 465)
  - 20:23 Kline Biology Laboratory (219 Prospect St)
    - 21 drawings, undated (Box 499)
    - Transverse (Folder 605)
    - Equipment Plans - No. 1 Hoods, 1965 (Box 814)
    - Equipment Plans - No. 3 Lab, 5th -7th Floors, 1965 (Box 815)
    - Equipment Plans - No. 3 Lab, 5th -7th Floors, 1965 (Box 816)
    - Equipment Plans - No. 4 Lab, 8th -11th Floors, 1965 (Box 817)
    - Steam Heated Water Baths, 1965 (Box 826)
    - N.I.H. set of plans, 1962-1963 (Box 910)
  - 20:25 Pierson-Sage parking structure, presentation drawings (3), 1973 (Folder 606)
  - 20: Mason Hall or Sloane Physics Building, Plans (25), 1911-1912 (Folder 632)
  - 20: 339 Edwards St., 1st-3rd Floor Plans (3), undated (Box 521)
  - 21:4 Heliostat Building
    - Plan and section; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 November (Box 574)
    - Detail of balcony and ladder to lens pier; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 July (Box 574)
    - Survey of apparatus; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 July (Box 574)
    - Setting for camera in tower; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 October (Box 574)
    - Revised detail of lower end of tube; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 July (Box 574)
    - Detail showing relation of instruments and building sheet; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 July (Box 574)
    - Plans and sections; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 June (Box 574)
    - Elevations of tower; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 June (Box 574)
    - Plan of steel frame and track for roof; L.W. Robinson, architect, 1915 July (Box 574)
    - alterations (2 drawings), undated (Folder 500)
  - 21:6 Sterling Divinity Quadrangle (409 Prospect St)
    - 16 drawings, undated (Folder 501)
    - Yale Divinity School [?] (2 drawings), 1931 (Box 679)
    - Divinity School, 1951 (Folder 834)
    - Architectural Details, 1931 (Box 820, Box 820a–820d)
    - Miscellaneous Buildings
    - Proposed Shopping Center - Howe St., Dwight St., George St., 1951 (Box 808)
    - Old Cross High School, 1957 (Box 821)
    - Old Cross High School, 1957 (Box 822)
    - Old Cross High School, 1957 (Box 823)
    - Old Cross High School, 1957 (Box 824)
    - Apartment/Dormitory Proposal, Site Map (8) and Floor Plans (9) (Folder 630)
    - 2nd Floor Plan. Copy, 1931 January 19 (Folder 630)
    - Ground Plan, undated (Folder 633)
  - 21:13 309 Edwards St. (5 drawings), undated (Box 499)
  - 21:18 Whitehall Aspartments, Prospect and Canner Streets (2 drawings), undated (Box 499)
  - 21: Library Shelving Facility (Leeder Hill Rd)
    - Architectural and structural drawing -Bid set, 1998 January 2 (Box 723)
    - Architectural and structural drawing -Constructural set, 1998 January 20 (Box 723)
    - Architectural and structural drawing -Bid set, 1998 January 2 (Box 724)
    - Architectural and structural drawing -Constructural set, 1998 January 20 (Box 724)
  - 22:25 Anthony H. Brady Memorial Laboratory (310 Cedar St): shop drawings (6 drawings), undated (Box 499)
  - 22:26 Boardman Administration (330 Cedar St): tunnel proposal (2 drawings), undated (Box 499)
  - 22:28 Yale Army Lab School
    - Pathological Laboratory; L.W. Robinson, 1918 August (Box 574)
    - Foundation plan, sheet 1; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Layout of heating and plumbing, sheet 1P; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Ground floor plan, sheet 2; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Elevations and sections, sheet 3; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Layout of framing (at braced bays) sheet 3A; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Detail of laboratory tables, sheet 21; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Detail of radiator, sheet 22; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Typical layout of radiators and connections, sheet 23; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Plumbing details, sheet 24; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Box 574)
    - Layout showing relation of. returns, etc, to seal leg, sheet #24; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Folder 649)
    - Plumbing details, sheet #1; J. Byers Holbrook, C.E.; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Folder 649)
    - Plumbing details, sheet #2.; J, Byers Holbrook, C.E.; L.W. Robinson, 1918 September (Folder 649)
    - Set III - Foundation plan (Bid set); L.W. Robinson, 1918 August (Folder 649)
    - Set III - Ground floor plan (Bid set); L.W. Robinson, 1918 August (Folder 649)
    - Set III - South (Congress Avenue) elevation (bid set); L.W. Robinson, 1918 August (Folder 649)
  - 22:50 Sterling Hall of Medicine (333 Cedar St) (138 drawings)
    - Drawings, some watercolors, undated (Box 506A, Folder 506)
    - Drawings, undated (Folder 507)
    - Drawings, undated (Folder 508)
    - Drawings, undated (Box 509)
    - Drawings, undated (Box 510)
    - Yale Medical group, 2 copies, undated (Box 614)
    - Tunnel or sub-basement plan (Box 614)
    - Ground floor plan (Box 614)
    - Entrance floor plan (Box 614)
    - 1st floor plan (Box 614)
    - 2nd floor plan (Box 614)
    - 3rd floor plan (Box 614)
    - 4th floor plan (Box 614)
    - Pathology-Medical School (13 drawings), 1972 (Box 679)
    - Medical Library, alteration; Douglas Orr, 1975 March 11 (Box 614)
    - Medical Library expansion (Box 614)
    - Architectural floor plan, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Architectural elevations and sections, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Elevations and details area plan, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - New office partitions and shelving, reading room area, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Mechanical, undated (Box 614)
    - Finish schedule, 1975 October 21-22 (Box 614)
    - Architectural elevations and sections, 1975 October 21 (Box 614)
    - no date (Box 614)
    - no date (Box 614)
    - Medical Library alteration; Douglas Orr, 1975 March 12-19 (Box 614)
    - Medical Library alteration; Douglas Orr, 1974 February 24 (Box 614)
    - Medical Library expansion (Box 614)
    - New office partitions and shelving, reading room area alternate #1, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Mechanical, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Electrical plan: power, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Electrical plan: lighting, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Architectural floor plan, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Architectural elevations and sections, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Elevations and details area plan, alternate # LCI door work, 1976 January 14 (Box 614)
    - Study for projected library (2 copies), Grosvenor Atterbury, architect; John Thompkins, associated, 1935 October (Folder 644)
    - Plot plan (Folder 644)
    - Longitudinal section (Folder 644)
    - Basement floor (Folder 644)
    - First floor (Folder 644)
    - Second floor (Folder 644)
    - Third floor (Folder 644)
    - Drawings for projected library, 1937 March 11 (Folder 644)
    - Basement plan (Folder 644)
    - First floor plan (Folder 644)
    - Second floor plan (Folder 644)
    - Drawings for projected library wing (2 copies), Grosvenor Atterbury, architect; John Thompkins, associated, 1937 May (Folder 644A)
    - East elevation (Folder 644A)
    - Basement floor (Folder 644A)
    - First floor (Folder 644A)
    - Second floor (Folder 644A)
    - Plot plan (1 copy) (Folder 644A)
    - Drawings for library extension (2 copies), Grosvenor Atterbury, architect; Frank Dvorak, associated, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - Plot plan, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - Cross-section and longitudinal section, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - Sub-basement and foundation plan, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - Basement plan, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - First floor plan, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - Second floor plan, 1939 October (Folder 644A)
    - Drawing for library extension, 1939 November 29 (Folder 644A)
    - Longitudinal section, 1939 November 29 (Folder 644A)
    - Drawing for library extension, 1940 January 25 (Folder 644A)
    - Plan of historical section, 1940 January 25 (Folder 644A)
    - First floor, stack rooms 100-109, 1940 January 25 (Folder 644A)
    - Second floor, stack rooms 200-209, 1940 January 25 (Folder 644A)
    - Original drawings of floors, undated (Folder 644)
    - Plans for sub-basement, basement, first floor, and second floor and building data (2 drawings); Martin, Horton and Associates, Luchini and Milfort, 1987 June 22 (Box 626)
    - Renovation drawings, 1971-1990
      - Color Schemes (Tagboard) (Folder 615)
      - Circulation Room, Rotunda and Information Room Elevations (Tagboard) (Folder 615)
      - Windows and Stairs (Tagboard) (Folder 615)
      - First Floor Plan (Tagboard) (Folder 615)
      - Temporary Exits (Tagboard) (Folder 615)
      - The Harvey Cushing / John Hay Whitney Medical Library Blueprint Book (169 drawings) (Box 616)
      - Sets of Relocation Sketches (4 drawings) (Folder 617)
      - Sub-basement Plan (Folder 617)
      - Phasing Plans (3 drawings) (Folder 617)
      - Plans, elevations, schedules, sections, site plan, studies (Box 614)
      - Plans, elevations, schedules, sections, site plan, studies (Box 619)
      - Plans, elevations, schedules, sections, site plan, studies (Box 620)
      - Plans, elevations, schedules, sections, site plan, studies (Folder 622)
      - Notes and Schedules Blueprint Book (152 drawings) (Box 622A)
      - Notes and Schedules Blueprint Book (152 drawings) (Box 622B)
      - Notes and Schedules Blueprint Book (152 drawings) (Box 622C)
      - Furnishings (Box 779)
      - Progress Print Blueprint Book (72 drawings) (Box 779)
      - Progress Print Blueprint Book (72 drawings) (Box 780)
  - 22:51 Sterling Power Plant (309 Congress Ave) (4 drawings), undated (Folder 511)
  - 22:67 Farnam Memorial Building: details (7 drawings), undated (Box 512)
  - 22:68 Lauder Hall (310 Cedar St) (4 drawings), undated (Box 512)
  - 22:98 Clinic Building, circa 1929, undated (Folder 514, Folder 587)
  - 22:99 Raleigh Fitkin Memorial Pavilion: proposal (4 drawings), undated (Box 512)